Ashley Leonard

803)226-1926 amlockhart24@gmail.com

Professional Summary

I've developed in my career path beginning in customer service and hospitality management expanding into a communications expert role. I thrive in service-oriented environments, specializing in vendor relations. My current field of study of Web Development in content, graphics, and navigation provides a positive user experience. My previous career path in customer service in mediating, leading team development and mentoring individuals success. I've successfully managed a growing business and created a team environment. I've attended the University of South Carolina Aiken and continued my education by attending a Coding Bootcamp through Clubhou.se in August, GA.

Highlights

- Excellent oral and written communications
- Event Planning
- Computer program knowledge and technology literacy
- Organizational expertise- managing database, files and records
- Proven managerial skills and conflict resolution

Experience

Communications Specialist, The Reserve Club at Woodside

March 2019-Present

- Specialized in content curation for members and employee communications
- Organized event details and coordinated with vendors and guests
- Developed user friendly webpages for membership website
- · Technical support for membership and employees
- Scheduled daily activities and events for guests and employees
- Ordered office supplies and processed payments
- Acted as gatekeeper for sensitive information
- Attended and took minutes for meetings, coordinated board meetings and employee training

Technical Service Coordinator, Allen Precision Equipment

August 2018-March 2019

- · Responsible for informing customer service, sales, and management on delays and problems related
- Received and prepared all equipment work orders for inside and outside repairs and services
- Recorded and maintained files and records of customer requests, work or services performed, charges and inventory needed for repairs
- · Ordered supplies, parts, and equipment directly for vendors
- Handled all rental requests, billing contracts and inventory for rental department
- · Registered and input all warranties for new equipment
- · Responsible for selling our in-house warranties on new/used equipment as well as annual warranty renewals

Technical Writer, NS Creative Solutions

April 2018- August 2019

- Centralized content library and conducted research on industry news and trends.
- · Curated content for an underground mining company
- Prepared instruction manuals, journal articles and newsletters.
- · Created and executed social media strategies.
- Coordinated travel for company, scheduled conferences, managed travel expenses
- Manage Facebook, Twitter, Reddit, Instagram, Medium social media platforms

Store Manager, Starbucks

May 2017- April 2018

- Exceeded Sales Target by 30-40% three months into Store Manager role
- Reduced turnover by 60% in 6 months
- Scheduled to forecast 0.0-0.1% variance of 40+ employees
- Managed a high-volume store under operational standards of excellence
- Submitted payroll for 40+ employees weekly, maintained employee's hourly preference and benefit eligibility
- Modeled Starbuck leadership standards, evaluating knowledge gaps, coaching towards understanding and developing talent
- Reporting metrics to the district and Atlanta regional offices; Revenue, COGS, Controllable Contribution, Profit & Loss Reports, Food Management, Labor Schedule vs Forecast
- · Ensuring customer satisfaction with interpersonal skills, focusing on building community and trust

Shift Supervisor, Starbucks

January 2013- May 2017

- Certified as; Coffee Master, Barista Trainer, IPLD Candidate, Barista Champion Area 92 2016
- Created a positive team environment by following operational policies and procedures
- · Assisted with interview process, hiring and maintaining talent

Chemical Biological Radiologic & Nuclear (CBRN) Specialist (74D), Army Reserves

March 2009- March 2014

- Provided training advice and supervision regarding CBRN equipment and operations
- Operated and maintained equipment in nuclear, biologically and chemically contaminated areas
- BCT Ft. Jackson, AIT Ft. Leonard Wood, 414th TC Co Orangeburg SC

Education

- Clubhou.se Code Bootcamp | Augusta, GA | September 2019 December 2019
- The University of South Carolina | Aiken, SC | B.A. Communications 2014-Continuing Education
- Aiken Technical College | Aiken, SC | 2012-2014 General Education

Skills

Java Script, GitHub, HTML, CSS, PHP, Visual Studios, Microsoft Office, MAC OSX, Windows OS, Microsoft Excel, Data analytics, Hootsuite, Buffer, BuzzSumo, MailChimp, Monday, Slack, Wordpress, Canva, Survey Monkey, QuickBooks, Relational database management systems (RDBMS), Adobe Creative Suite, Management, Leadership, Conflict Resolution, Customer Service, Customer Satisfaction, Team Building, Office Administration, Technical Writing, Social Media Content Creation/ Management,